http://www.snpolytechnic.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
You are hereHomePrivacy Policy
Privacy & Security Statement
Six Nations Polytechnic (SNP) is committed to respecting your privacy and protecting your personal information whether you are browsing for information or conducting business with us electronically. This Privacy & Security Statement explains the current practices employed at our web sites and is based upon the principles covered in Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act ("PIPEDA") as well as Ontario's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act ("FIPPA").
Privacy of Personal Information.
SNP does not share personal information that is provided voluntarily through web forms or other means, including standard web server log files. If you have supplied your email address, SNP may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with SNP and our products.
Web Server Log Files
SNP uses standard web server log files to collect site visitation statistics. Web server logging does collect machine-specific information such as IP address, operating system, and web browser type. Logs may also provide information about user pathways through the web site. The College collects this information in order to understand how its web site is used and to plan for future enhancements to the web site.
Cookies
The web site uses cookies. Cookies support the site visitation statistics process and support functions such as forms processing. Visitors to our web site may reject any or all of our cookies by using their web browser's preferences. Site visitors should be aware that certain features of the web site, such as forms and surveys, require the use of cookies to function properly.
Trademarks
SNP and all other names, logos, seals, or other symbols that are representative of the College are trademarks of use. Reproduction, copying, or redistribution of trademarks, without the written permission of SNP, is prohibited.
General Web Disclaimer
SNP makes web resources available to all of the community but does not review, edit, or endorse all items accessible from these pages. Personal and non-departmental web pages are not official statements of the College, and SNP is not responsible for the content of these page. We strive to ensure the accuracy of material on the web but discrepancies may existbetween printed and electronic information. In any such case please contact the site owner directly.
Opinions expressed in personal or non-departmental web pages should be construed as those of their authors, who are solely responsible for the information contained therein. If you have questions or comments about a particular page or document, please contact its site owner.
Some web pages contain links to web pages created by sources outside of the College. The existence of these links does not suggest any implicit or explicit approval of or endorsement of the linked web pages and their content by the College.
If you have any general comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about SNP's web pages, please direct them to info@snpolytechnic.com
Although SNP does not routinely screen or monitor content posted by users to the web site, the College reserves the right to remove content which violates the terms of this statement or other relevant policies, but is under no obligation to do so.
